

Hudson Kennedy
FULLSTACK DEVELOPER
SOFTWARE ENGINEER
UI/UX DESIGNER

CONTACT

Address:

Engoá street, 167 - Rio de Janeiro -Brazil

Phone:

(21) 9 6960-9121

Portfolio:

https://hudsonkennedy.vercel.app

E-mail:

hudsonhugo90@gmail.com

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ hudsonkennedyjr/

Github:

https://github.com/Hudsonjr90

Instagram:

https://www.instagram.com/ _hudson.9ki/



Graduated in Management Processes, with an emphasis on Process Management and Optimization, and I have always had the desire to acquire more knowledge and evolve professionally, I got in touch with the technology area about 10 years ago and since the end of 2019, I have returned to the technology area. where I've been studying and taking different courses. In 2021 I started my MBA in Software Engineering, where I have learned many new things and evolved day by day.

I will continue to improve myself daily as a Front-end Developer and Software Engineer after graduation, seeking to acquire more experience and knowledge!



EXPERIENCE

Full Technical Consultant

January 2022 - April 2022

DT3 Sports

Invoice issuance, marketplaces, content creation for campaigns, website development in React.JS, image optimization and responsible for the integration of ERP Bling.

VILT Brazil Information Systems

Adobe Experience Manager(AEM),

using Platform programs

providing services for

Fullstack Consulting, working with Java

in Backend and Angular/React in Frontend,

several clients such as Porto, CVC and etc.

E-commerce Analyst / Front-end Developer

February 2019 - June 2021

Nova Lik Auto Peças

Issuance of Sales Invoice
Issuance of Payment Reports
Input and Output of Products in Stock.

Office Assistant

November 2014 - June 2018

M

Quality and Service Technician

June 2010 - July 2013

Arcos Dourados LTDA.

Make employees work coordinated in their respective functions, for better customer service and delivery of a 100% qualitative product.

ACADEMIC EDUCATION

Faculdade Única

2021 - 2022

MBA Software Engineering

Estácio de Sá - RJ

2018 - 2020

TECHNOLOGIST Management processes



Hudson Kennedy
FULLSTACK DEVELOPER
SOFTWARE ENGINEER
UI/UX DESIGNER

CONTACT

Address:

Engoá street, 167 - Rio de Janeiro -Brazil

Phone:

(21) 9 6960-9121

Portfolio:

https://hudsonkennedy.vercel.app

E-mail:

hudsonhugo90@gmail.com

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ hudsonkennedyjr/

Github:

https://github.com/Hudsonjr90

Instagram:

https://www.instagram.com/ _hudson.9kj/



HTML/CSS/Jquery/Javascript/Angular/React/VueJs/NodeJs
3 Years of Experience
Git/Github/NPM/YARN/Wordpress/Shopify/Bling
3 Years of Experience
Bootstrap/Typescript/UI/UX/Figma/Photoshop
2 Years of Experience
Less/Sass
1 Year of Experience



EXTRACURRICULAR COURSES

Bootcamp Eduzz - Fullstack Developer - Digital Innovation - 2022
Adobe Professional – AEM Sites Business Practitioner - 2022
Adobe Professional – AEM Front-End Developer - 2022
DIO - Working with Components in React - 2022
DIO - Component architecture and front-end complexity
management - 2022
Let's Code Course (Santander) - Dev Fullstack - 2021
MERN Stack Course (MongoDB, Express, React & NodeJS FaculdadeIV2 - 2021
Initial Vuejs Course – Vuejs Brazil – 2021
Basic to Advanced Javascript & Typescript Course (HTML/CSS/
NodeJs/React/MySQL/PostgreSQL/MariaDB/ – Udemy – 2020



LANGUAGES

Spanish - Basic French - Basic Italian - Basic English - Advanced



ADDITIONAL ACTIVITIES

Excel/Word /Power Point
Teams/Outlook/Skype
Wordpress/Shopify/ERP Bling
System Configurations
Windows
Computer Domain
Typing
Document Archiving
Internet in general
Google Chrome/Mozilla/Opera